export  const Quizdata=[{
    question:"1. It was Sunday on Jan 1, 2006. What was the day of the week Jan 1, 2010?",
    options:["Sunday","Saturday","Friday","Wednesday"],
    answer:3
},{
    question:"2. What was the day of the week on 28th May, 2006?",
    options:["Thrusday","Friday","Saturday","Sunday"],
    answer:4
},{
    question:"3. What was the day of the week on 17th June, 1998?",
    options:["Monday","Tuesday","Wednesday","Thursday"],
    answer:3
},{
    question:"4. What will be the day of the week 15th August, 2010?",
    options:["Sunday","Monday","Tuesday","Friday"],
    answer:1
},{
    question:"5. Today is Monday. After 61 days, it will be:",
    options:["Wednesday","Saturday" ,"Tuesday ","Thursday"   ],
    answer:2
},{
    question:"6. 1.It was Sunday on Jan 1, 2006. What was the day of the week Jan 1, 2010?",
    options:["Sunday","Saturday","Friday","Wednesday"],
    answer:3
},{
    question:"7. What was the day of the week on 28th May, 2006?",
    options:["Thrusday","Friday","Saturday","Sunday"],
    answer:4
},{
    question:"8. What was the day of the week on 17th June, 1998?",
    options:["Monday","Tuesday","Wednesday","Thursday"],
    answer:3
},{
    question:"9. What will be the day of the week 15th August, 2010?",
    options:["Sunday","Monday","Tuesday","Friday"],
    answer:1
},{
    question:"10. Today is Monday. After 61 days, it will be:",
    options:["Wednesday","Saturday" ,"Tuesday ","Thursday"   ],
    answer:2
}];

export const tru=[true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true];